* Solutions

Privacy Policy
==============

Legal

This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which proinity LLC d/b/a KeyCDN ("KeyCDN") collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users (each, a "User") of the keycdn.com websites ("Site"). This privacy policy applies to the Site and all products and services offered by KeyCDN.

The legal responsible, hereinafter also "we" or "our", within meaning of the General Data Protection Regulation and other national data laws of the member states as well as other data protection regulations, is the:

proinity LLC  
Reichenauweg 1  
8272 Ermatingen  
Switzerland  

Personal Identification Information
-----------------------------------

We may collect personal identification information from Users in a variety of ways, including, but not limited to, when Users visit our site, register on the site, place an order, subscribe to the newsletter, respond to a survey, fill out a form, and in connection with other activities, services, features or resources we make available on our Site. As part of your Account information, KeyCDN collects and stores information, including full name, email address, IP address, billing address, phone number and business details such as VAT number. Users may, however, visit our Site anonymously. We will collect personal identification information from Users only if they voluntarily submit such information to us. Users can always refuse to supply personally identification information, except that it may prevent them from engaging in certain Site related activities.

Non-personal Identification Information
---------------------------------------

We may collect non-personal identification information about Users whenever they interact with our Site. Non-personal identification information may include the browser name, the type of computer and technical information about Users means of connection to our Site, such as the operating system and the Internet service providers utilized and other similar information.

Web Browser Cookies
-------------------

Our Site may use "cookies" to enhance User experience. User's web browser places cookies on their hard drive for record-keeping purposes and sometimes to track information about them. User may choose to set their web browser to refuse cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. If they do so, note that some parts of the Site may not function properly.

How We Use Collected Information
--------------------------------

KeyCDN may collect and use Users personal information for the following purposes:

* ### To improve customer service
    
    Information you provide helps us respond to your customer service requests and support needs more efficiently.
    
* ### To personalize user experience
    
    We may use information in the aggregate to understand how our Users as a group use the services and resources provided on our Site.
    
* ### To improve our site
    
    We may use feedback you provide to improve our products and services.
    
* ### To detect fraud
    
    The collected data allows us protecting against or identifying possible fraudulent activities.
    
* ### To process payments
    
    We may use the information Users provide about themselves when placing an order only to provide service to that order. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to provide the service.
    
* ### To run a promotion, contest, survey or other Site feature
    
    To send Users information they agreed to receive about topics we think will be of interest to them.
    
* ### To send periodic emails
    
    We may use the email address to send User information and updates pertaining to their order. It may also be used to respond to their inquiries, questions, and/or other requests. If User decides to opt-in to our mailing list, they will receive emails that may include company news, updates, related product or service information, etc. If at any time the User would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, they may do so by contacting us via our Site.

How We Protect Your Information
-------------------------------

We adopt appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures to protect against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of your personal information, username, password, transaction information and data stored on our Site. Sensitive and private data exchange between the Site and its Users happens over a TLS secured communication channel.

Sharing Your Personal Information
---------------------------------

We do not sell, trade, or rent Users personal identification information to others. We may share generic aggregated demographic information not linked to any personal identification information regarding visitors and users with our business partners, trusted affiliates and advertisers for the purposes outlined above.

Removal of Data
---------------

In the event that a customer wants to remove any personal data that was previously collected, KeyCDN will permanently delete such data. Please contact our support team directly to do so.

There are certain third party services where all customer information will be delete instantly upon customer request while there are other third party services where the customer information might not be deleted instantly. For example, if a customer wants to have their contact information removed from our email delivery service provider, this can be done immediately. However, in terms of billing related data, this is required by law to keep for 10 years. Credit card details are not stored with us anyway.

When personal data gets removed from our systems, the data is still present in backups. This is to better serve our customers in the event that someone accidentally deleted their account or for disaster recovery purposes. Backups are securely stored and isolated from any further processing. They will get fully deleted when the retention period ends.

Data Portability
----------------

KeyCDN customers can ask to receive their personal data in a commonly used format. Contact KeyCDN support to request this information and provide your PGP public key in order to receive the data encrypted by email.

Managing your Information
-------------------------

We communicate with users who subscribe to our services via email. We use your email address to confirm your opening of an account, to send you notice of payments, to send you information about changes to our products and services or to provide those products or services, and to send notices and other disclosures as required by law. Generally, users cannot opt out of these communications, but they will be primarily informational in nature rather than promotional.

We provide you the opportunity to exercise an opt-out choice if you do not want to receive other types of communication from us. This includes things such as updates from us regarding new features or general web development and/or performance topics.

We're committed to keep your data accurate and up to date, to the extent that you provide us with the information we need to do so. If your data changes (for example, if you have a new email address), then you are responsible for updating that information in the KeyCDN dashboard.

Upon request, we will provide you with information about whether we hold, or process on behalf of a third party, any of your Personal Information. The retention period shall not exceed the duration of our business relationship with you unless we have a legitimate business interest need to retain the information for a longer period. We may also retain and use your information in order to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, prevent abuse or to enforce our agreements.

Third Party Service GDPR and Privacy Shield Compliance
------------------------------------------------------

At times, we use third party services to help better serve our customers. Our email delivery service provider is an example of this. In this case, customer information such as an email address is shared with the third party service, provided the customer has given consent to receive emails from us.

We've audited the third party services used at KeyCDN and as far as we know, they are GDPR compliant and Privacy Shield certified.

Your Acceptance of These Terms
------------------------------

By using this Site, you signify your acceptance of this policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our Site. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes.

Contacting Us
-------------

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this site, please [contact us](https://www.keycdn.com/contact).

Last updated May 25th, 2018

#### Product

#### Company

#### Support

© 2024 proinity LLC  
Made in Switzerland

×

KeyCDN uses cookies to make its website easier to use. [Learn more](https://www.keycdn.com/privacy) ×
